rbrides.com 2016-12-08

# RBrides.com Privacy Policy

**Our Commitment To Privacy:**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

_The Information We Collect: Your Name, E-mail, City and Country._

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on RBrides.com website.   
On some pages, you can order products/subscriptions, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: _Your Name, E-mail, Delivery Address, City and Country_. The Way We Use Information: _For Your Profile_ / _Delivery Services_. 

**Our Commitment To Data Security **

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by your general information. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.   
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

**Use of Information Obtained by RBrides.com**

**Private Information:**

We use e-mail addresses submitted by members when sending notifications about new incoming messages ( _you have a new flift / new letter at RBrides.com_ ) or new profiles. Responders' e-mail addresses are not disclosed to the original sender nor is any other personally identifiable information. Your e-mail preferences can be changed at any time by logging onto your account, going to the "Edit Your "General information"" setting at the botton of the page. 

E-mail and delivery addresses may also be used in private correspondence with the user for customer service issues. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for services. RBrides.com utilizes a third party service provider for credit card processing to facilitate the user's transaction and the service provider does not use personal information provided by the site for its own promotional purposes. All other private information submitted by the user is confidential and will not be disclosed except as required by law or to protect members of www.RBrides.com. All private information can be updated or deleted by the user at any time.

**How To Contact Us:** ****  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please contact us at 

Or by regular mail:   
Addresses for correspondence:

MADINA GROUP LTD., Suite 102, Ground Floor, Blake Building, Corner Eyre & Hutson Str, Belize

BIGZUR LP, SUMMIT HOUSE, 4-5 MITCHELL STREET, EDINBURGH, SCOTLAND, EH6 7BD, UNITED KINGDOM

Office location:  
MADINA GROUP LTD., LAVRENIEVA 4, 420126, KAZAN, RUSSIA
